var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "ever",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيُؤْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "soon He will give him",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "fasayu'tīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتِكُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah will give you",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "yu'tikumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثَرِ",
        "answer": "(the) trace",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "athari",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "a reward",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "a reward",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْرًا",
        "answer": "and a reward",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "wa-ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَأْخُذُوهَا",
        "answer": "to take it",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "litakhudhūhā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْخُذُونَهَا",
        "answer": "that they will take",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "yakhudhūnahā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْخُذُونَهَا",
        "answer": "that you will take it",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "takhudhūnahā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأَخَّرَ",
        "answer": "will follow",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ta-akhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "And others",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "wa-ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآزَرَهُ",
        "answer": "then strengthens it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faāzarahu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصِيلًا",
        "answer": "and evening",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣīlan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1238",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1239",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1240",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1241",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1242",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who",
        "pcklId": "1243",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1244",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1245",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1246",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "1247",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1248",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2486",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah may help you",
        "pcklId": "2487",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2488",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "2489",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2490",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "about Allah",
        "pcklId": "2491",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah s wrath (is)",
        "pcklId": "2492",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2493",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "2494",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2495",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2496",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2497",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2498",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2499",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2500",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2501",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2502",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2503",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2504",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah said",
        "pcklId": "2505",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah will give you",
        "pcklId": "2506",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2507",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah was pleased",
        "pcklId": "2508",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2509",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised you",
        "pcklId": "2510",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah encompassed",
        "pcklId": "2511",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2512",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2513",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in (the) way of Allah",
        "pcklId": "2514",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2515",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "That Allah may admit",
        "pcklId": "2516",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Then Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "2517",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2518",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "2519",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "2520",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2521",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is the) Messenger of Allah",
        "pcklId": "2522",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "from Allah",
        "pcklId": "2523",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "2524",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "643",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "644",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "645",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "That you may believe",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "litu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "(has) not believed",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "yu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "601",
        "tlit": "āminīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) faith",
        "pcklId": "637",
        "tlit": "īmānan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their faith",
        "pcklId": "638",
        "tlit": "īmānihim",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the believers",
        "pcklId": "817",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believing men",
        "pcklId": "818",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "and the believers",
        "pcklId": "819",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "820",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "for the believers",
        "pcklId": "821",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "822",
        "tlit": "mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "823",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْمِنَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the believing women",
        "pcklId": "861",
        "tlit": "wal-mu'mināti",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنَاتٌ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "862",
        "tlit": "mu'minātun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلُونَا",
        "answer": "and our families",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlūnā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their families",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "ahlīhim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهَا",
        "answer": "and worthy of it",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولِي",
        "answer": "possessors of military might",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسٍ",
        "answer": "possessors of military might",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "basin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَدِّلُوا",
        "answer": "change",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yubaddilū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْدِيلًا",
        "answer": "any change",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tabdīlan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُبَشِّرًا",
        "answer": "and (as) a bearer of glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "wamubashiran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَطْنِ",
        "answer": "within",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bibaṭni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْتَغُونَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yabtaghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُكْرَةً",
        "answer": "morning",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "buk'ratan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْلُغَ",
        "answer": "reaching",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yablugha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُورًا",
        "answer": "ruined",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "būran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَايِعُونَكَ",
        "answer": "pledge allegiance to you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yubāyiʿūnaka",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَايِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they pledge allegiance",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yubāyiʿūna",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبَايِعُونَكَ",
        "answer": "they pledged allegiance to you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yubāyiʿūnaka",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among themselves",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينًا",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "tlit": "mubīnan",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّبِعْكُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) follow you",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "nattabiʿ'kum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُونَا",
        "answer": "will you follow us",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿūnā",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتَ",
        "answer": "under",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "taḥta",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُتِمَّ",
        "answer": "and complete",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wayutimma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَثَابَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and rewarded them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-athābahum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "had put",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and He made",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "fajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنُودُ",
        "answer": "(are the) hosts",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "junūdu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنُودُ",
        "answer": "(are the) hosts",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "junūdu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(to) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(to) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِيَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of the time of) ignorance",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-jāhiliyati",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٌ",
        "answer": "any blame",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥarajun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٌ",
        "answer": "any blame",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥarajun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٌ",
        "answer": "any blame",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥarajun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāmi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرَامَ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarāma",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْسُدُونَنَا",
        "answer": "you envy us",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taḥsudūnanā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَقَّ",
        "answer": "more deserving",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "aḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the true",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمًا",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "ḥakīman",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمًا",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "ḥakīman",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَكِيمًا",
        "answer": "All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "ḥakīman",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحَلِّقِينَ",
        "answer": "having shaved",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "muḥalliqīna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحِلَّهُ",
        "answer": "its place (of sacrifice)",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "maḥillahu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمِيَّةَ",
        "answer": "disdain ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamiyata",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيَّةَ",
        "answer": "(the) disdain",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ḥamiyyata",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَاطَ",
        "answer": "Allah encompassed",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aḥāṭa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Aware",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "khabīran",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "(which) sends forth",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخَلَّفُونَ",
        "answer": "those who remained behind",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-mukhalafūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخَلَّفُونَ",
        "answer": "those who remained behind",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-mukhalafūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُخَلَّفِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who remained behind",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "lil'mukhallafīna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "passed away",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافُونَ",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "takhāfūna",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَدْبَارَ",
        "answer": "the backs",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-adbāra",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَدْخُلُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely, you will enter",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "latadkhulunna",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُدْخِلَ",
        "answer": "That He may admit",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "liyud'khila",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْخِلْهُ",
        "answer": "He will admit him",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yud'khil'hu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُدْخِلَ",
        "answer": "That Allah may admit",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "liyud'khila",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَتُدْعَوْنَ",
        "answer": "You will be called",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "satud'ʿawna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَائِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(is) a turn",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "dāiratu",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدِينِ",
        "answer": "and (the) religion",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wadīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religions",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَنْبِكَ",
        "answer": "your sins",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "dhanbika",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your heads",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ruūsakum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "You see them",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "tarāhum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّؤْيَا",
        "answer": "vision",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "l-ru'yā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالٌ",
        "answer": "(for) men",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "rijālun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمًا",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "raḥīman",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُحَمَاءُ",
        "answer": "and merciful",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "ruḥamāu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "[We] have sent you",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) sent",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "arsala",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولُ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "l-rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "rasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "His Messenger s",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "rasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "rasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Messenger of Allah",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَضِيَ",
        "answer": "Allah was pleased",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "raḍiya",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِضْوَانًا",
        "answer": "and pleasure",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wariḍ'wānan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُكَّعًا",
        "answer": "bowing",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "rukkaʿan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "They wish",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزُّرَّاعَ",
        "answer": "the sowers",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-zurāʿa",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَزَرْعٍ",
        "answer": "(is) like a seed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "kazarʿin",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَزْدَادُوا",
        "answer": "that they may increase",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "liyazdādū",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزَيَّلُوا",
        "answer": "they had been apart",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tazayyalū",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزُيِّنَ",
        "answer": "that was made fair-seeming",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wazuyyina",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُسَبِّحُوهُ",
        "answer": "and glorify Him",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "watusabbiḥūhu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّجُودِ",
        "answer": "(of) the prostration",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-sujūdi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدِ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-masjidi",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسْجِدَ",
        "answer": "Al-Masjid Al-Haraam",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-masjida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "and prostrating",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعِيرًا",
        "answer": "a Blazing Fire",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "saʿīran",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّكِينَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] tranquility",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-sakīnata",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّكِينَةَ",
        "answer": "the tranquility",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-sakīnata",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكِينَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His tranquility",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "sakīnatahu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "they will submit",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُنَّةَ",
        "answer": "(The established) way",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "sunnata",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسُنَّةِ",
        "answer": "in (the) way of Allah",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "lisunnati",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "and evil",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wasāat",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوْءِ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-sawi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوْءِ",
        "answer": "(of) evil",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-sawi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّوْءِ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-sawi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their misdeeds",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "sayyiātihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوقِهِ",
        "answer": "its stem",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "sūqihi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِيمَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their mark",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sīmāhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and it stands",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةِ",
        "answer": "the tree",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-shajarati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "shadīdin",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشِدَّاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) firm",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ashiddāu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "and the polytheist men",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "wal-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُشْرِكَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the polytheist women",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "wal-mush'rikāti",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطْأَهُ",
        "answer": "its shoot",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shaṭahu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَغَلَتْنَا",
        "answer": "Kept us busy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shaghalatnā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a Witness",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاهِدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a witness",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "shāhidan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدُّوكُمْ",
        "answer": "and hindered you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "waṣaddūkum",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَ",
        "answer": "Allah has fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطًا",
        "answer": "(to) a Path",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭan",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطًا",
        "answer": "(to the) Path",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭan",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتُصِيبَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and would befall you",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "fatuṣībakum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "(is the) destination",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "maṣīran",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "harm",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْطَلَقْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you set forth",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "inṭalaqtum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُطِيعُوا",
        "answer": "you obey",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tuṭīʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطِعِ",
        "answer": "obeys",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "yuṭiʿi",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْفَرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He gave you victory",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aẓfarakum",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you thought",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "And you assumed",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "waẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَّ",
        "answer": "an assumption",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَّ",
        "answer": "an assumption",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّانِّينَ",
        "answer": "who assume",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-ẓānīna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُظْهِرَهُ",
        "answer": "that He (may) make it prevail",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "liyuẓ'hirahu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْتَدْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] have prepared",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "aʿtadnā",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْجِبُ",
        "answer": "delighting",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'jibu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَجَّلَ",
        "answer": "and He has hastened",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "faʿajjala",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعَدَّ",
        "answer": "and prepared",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿadda",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَذِّبَ",
        "answer": "And He (may) punish",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wayuʿadhiba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُعَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "and punishes",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wayuʿadhibu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْكُمْ",
        "answer": "He will punish you",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'kum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَذِّبْهُ",
        "answer": "He will punish him",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yuʿadhib'hu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَذَّبْنَا",
        "answer": "surely, We would have punished",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "laʿadhabnā",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the Bedouins",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَابِ",
        "answer": "the Bedouins",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrābi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَجِ",
        "answer": "the lame",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-aʿraji",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعَرَّةٌ",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "maʿarratun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُعَزِّرُوهُ",
        "answer": "and (may) honor him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "watuʿazzirūhu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزًا",
        "answer": "mighty",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزًا",
        "answer": "(is) All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَزِيزًا",
        "answer": "All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ʿazīzan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْكُوفًا",
        "answer": "(was) prevented",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maʿkūfan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلِمَ",
        "answer": "and He knew",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "faʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you knew them",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūhum",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلِمَ",
        "answer": "But He knew",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "faʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "you knew",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "taʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "651",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "751",
        "tlit": "ʿalīman",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "(is) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "812",
        "tlit": "ʿalīman",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْمَىٰ",
        "answer": "the blind",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-aʿmā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاهَدَ",
        "answer": "he has covenanted",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ʿāhada",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَضِبَ",
        "answer": "and Allah s wrath (is)",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waghaḍiba",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَغْفِرَ",
        "answer": "That may forgive",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "liyaghfira",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرُ",
        "answer": "He forgives",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yaghfiru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "so ask forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورًا",
        "answer": "Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "ghafūran",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغْفِرَةً",
        "answer": "forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "maghfiratan",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَغْلَظَ",
        "answer": "then it becomes thick",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taghlaẓa",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغَانِمَ",
        "answer": "(the) spoils of war",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "maghānima",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَغَانِمَ",
        "answer": "And spoils of war",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wamaghānima",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَغَانِمَ",
        "answer": "spoils of war",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maghānima",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَغِيظَ",
        "answer": "that He (may) enrage",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "liyaghīẓa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَحْنَا",
        "answer": "We have given victory",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fataḥnā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتْحًا",
        "answer": "a victory",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fatḥan",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتْحًا",
        "answer": "(with) a victory",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fatḥan",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتْحًا",
        "answer": "a victory",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fatḥan",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلًا",
        "answer": "Bounty",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "faḍlan",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "understanding",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْزًا",
        "answer": "a success",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fawzan",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَ",
        "answer": "(is) over",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fawqa",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَاتِلُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you will fight them",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "tuqātilūnahum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاتَلَكُمُ",
        "answer": "fight you",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "qātalakumu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِرُوا",
        "answer": "you had power",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taqdirū",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Powerful",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "qadīran",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَدَّمَ",
        "answer": "preceded",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "taqaddama",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبًا",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "qarīban",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبًا",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "qarīban",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُقَصِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "and shortened",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wamuqaṣṣirīna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْقَلِبَ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yanqaliba",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِ",
        "answer": "(the) hearts",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "qulūbi",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hearts",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "qulūbikum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "qulūbihimu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "1476",
        "tlit": "sayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "1477",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1478",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "1479",
        "tlit": "sayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1480",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Allah said",
        "pcklId": "1481",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "Then they will say",
        "pcklId": "1482",
        "tlit": "fasayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1483",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمًا",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "644",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمًا",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "645",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةً",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "kathīratan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةً",
        "answer": "much",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "kathīratan",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُكَفِّرَ",
        "answer": "and (to) remove",
        "pcklId": "299",
        "tlit": "wayukaffira",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارِ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "l-kufāri",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفَّارَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "l-kufāra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَّ",
        "answer": "and has withheld",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wakaffa",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّ",
        "answer": "withheld",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kaffa",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "And sufficient is",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّهِ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "kullihi",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلَامَ",
        "answer": "(the) Words",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "kalāma",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةَ",
        "answer": "(to the) word",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "kalimata",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1202",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and is",
        "pcklId": "1203",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1204",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1205",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "and you became",
        "pcklId": "1206",
        "tlit": "wakuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "1207",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "1208",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and is",
        "pcklId": "1209",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَكُونَ",
        "answer": "that it may be",
        "pcklId": "1210",
        "tlit": "walitakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and is",
        "pcklId": "1211",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "1212",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "1213",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَ",
        "answer": "And is",
        "pcklId": "1214",
        "tlit": "wakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْزَمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and made them adhere",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-alzamahum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَلْسِنَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their tongues",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "bi-alsinatihim",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and He has cursed them",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "walaʿanahum",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "is not",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not is",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their similitude",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "mathaluhum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَثَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "And their similitude",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "wamathaluhum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرِيضِ",
        "answer": "the sick",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-marīḍi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "has power",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yamliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) kingdom",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْوَالُنَا",
        "answer": "our properties",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "amwālunā",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذِيرًا",
        "answer": "and (as) a warner",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wanadhīran",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "sent down",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "so He sent down",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "fa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "Then Allah sent down",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "fa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنِسَاءٌ",
        "answer": "and women",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wanisāon",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْصُرَكَ",
        "answer": "And Allah may help you",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wayanṣuraka",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرًا",
        "answer": "(with) a help",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "naṣran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "naṣīran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَتَهُ",
        "answer": "His favor",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matahu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "himself",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعًا",
        "answer": "a benefit",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "nafʿan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُنَافِقَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the hypocrite women",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "wal-munāfiqāti",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنَافِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the hypocrite men",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-munāfiqīna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكَثَ",
        "answer": "breaks (his oath)",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nakatha",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْكُثُ",
        "answer": "he breaks",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yankuthu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهْدِيَكَ",
        "answer": "and guide you",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "wayahdiyaka",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَهْدِيَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and He may guide you",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wayahdiyakum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْهَدْيَ",
        "answer": "while the offering",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "wal-hadya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "with guidance",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَ",
        "answer": "they would find",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "yajidūna",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدَ",
        "answer": "you will find",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "tajida",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their faces",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wujūhihim",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرُونَا",
        "answer": "Allow us",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "dharūnā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَئُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you may trample them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taṭaūhum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَكُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised you",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "waʿadakumu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "Allah has promised",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْفَىٰ",
        "answer": "fulfils",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "awfā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُوَقِّرُوهُ",
        "answer": "and respect him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watuwaqqirūhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) righteousness",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "l-taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوَلَّوُا",
        "answer": "surely they would turn",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "lawallawū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "you turn away",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "tatawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you turned away",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "tawallaytum",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "yatawalla",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيًّا",
        "answer": "any protector",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "waliyyan",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدُ",
        "answer": "(The) Hand",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "yadu",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَ",
        "answer": "(the) hands",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "aydiya",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "aydiyahum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَيْدِيَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your hands",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "wa-aydiyakum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "48",
        "ayah": "24"
    }
]; 
export default words;